Well, most recently, my gynecologist.
Oh, you stay as long as you'd like.
(Amy:)I'm glad to hear you say that
because I'm having a wonderful time.
(Amy:)Hmm. I said the same thing
to my gynecologist.
What are you gonna get
at the train store, Sheldon?
(Sheldon:)Oh, I'm not buying anything.
(Sheldon:)They're having a lecture.
"HO gage railroading.
HaIf the size of O gage,
but twice the fun."
It's a very controversial topic.
- Which side do you come down on?
- I'll let you know after tonight.
(Sheldon:)Unlike some people,
I'm going in with an open mind.
(Sheldon:)Who am I kidding?
(Sheldon:)Of course we all know
it's O gage or no gage.
(Howard:)Can you believe grown men
sit around and play with toy trains? Heh.
That's big talk...